Let's take a look at how to check if the virtual model is correctly inserted.
First, we will insert the character model into the scene.
We need to select the insert unit.
Choosing the wrong unit may cause problems.
You can refer to the floor grid.
Now the entire virtual model is about the same size as a floor grid.
Usually, for virtual models, only one corner needs to be connected to two floor grids.
We will create a template for the virtual model.
Then look at the conflict problems that may occur.
We will arrange the template around the virtual model.
Then look at the simulation.
You can see that the simulation quality is very low.
This is because the template produced according to the model is too small.
The particle diameter is too large.
The grid is too small.
Therefore, too small virtual models may cause the different default values ​​of the template to not match each other.
Consequently, various problems arise.
At this time, we need to re-insert a larger unit into the virtual model.
We can add a default virtual model to the work area as a comparison reference.
We can see that the self-defined virtual model is the opposite of the default size.
Such a virtual model
can continue to make clothing.